{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Redford",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Best_Actor_BAFTA_Award_winners",
    "human_readable": "Robert Redford is a subject of Best Actor BAFTA Award winners.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9134743809700012,
            "question": "Name an award-winning performance by Robert Redford."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9134273529052734,
            "question": "What award has Robert Redford won?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8603367209434509,
            "question": "What type of award did Robert Redford win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8101547360420227,
            "question": "Is Robert Redford known for acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8077099919319153,
            "question": "Who is Robert Redford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7622107267379761,
            "question": "What film roles is Robert Redford famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7477630972862244,
            "question": "Has Robert Redford received any prestigious awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7002449631690979,
            "question": "What are some of the films starring Robert Redford?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.640758752822876,
            "question": "What are some of Robert Redford's notable achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5472844243049622,
            "question": "In what category is Robert Redford recognized for his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Redford is a subject of Best Actor BAFTA Award winners.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6884_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Robert Redford's notable achievements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6884_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the films starring Robert Redford?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6884_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Robert Redford received any prestigious awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6884_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6884_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6884_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6884_141.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6884_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6884_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6884_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6884_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6884_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6884_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6884_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me explain why. While the provided text mentions Robert Redford's numerous accolades, including Golden Globes and an Academy Award for Best Director, it doesn't state that he has ever won a BAFTA Award for Best Actor. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while Robert Redford has had a long and illustrious career, including many nominations and wins, there is no mention of him being a subject of Best Actor BAFTA Award winners. The text does mention his numerous awards and nominations, including Golden Globe Awards and Academy Awards, but it specifically mentions that he was nominated for an Oscar (Academy Award) once for \"The Sting\" (1973), which suggests that he has not won the Best Actor BAFTA Award."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not mention any information about Robert Redford being a subject of Best Actor BAFTA Award winners. While the documents provide extensive details on his acting and directing career, including nominations for various awards like Oscars, Golden Globes, and Directors Guild of America Awards, there is no reference to him winning or being nominated for a Best Actor BAFTA Award."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text focuses on Redford's achievements as an actor, director, and producer, highlighting his Oscar wins and nominations, Golden Globe Awards, and other recognitions. There is no mention of any BAFTA Award wins or nominations for Best Actor.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Robert Redford has never won a BAFTA Award for Best Actor.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The provided context does not mention Robert Redford receiving a Best Actor BAFTA Award. While the information details his Oscar nominations, Golden Globe awards, and other accolades, there is no reference to him winning or being nominated for a BAFTA Award in the best actor category.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}